Contact

nursemonkey1@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/monicaurbieta%7Emadolora-7998474a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare Microsoft Word Research

Monica Urbieta~Madolora

*Aspiring OB High Risk Director-2020! *High Risk OB~Travel RN, *RN/VN Clinical & Theory Educator (Per Diem) Infusion RN (Per Diem) *PACU & Pre~Op Nurse (Per Diem *CMRN (Per Diem) San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

Wish list:

Peace, Love & Happiness

Faith:

What is meant for me will never pass me by...

A little about myself:

I graduated 5/2000, after attending, Orvis, School of Nursing, @ the University of NV, Reno.

I worked for a little over a year in Medical/Surgical/Oncology, where I gained a solid foundation, which has proven to be a huge foundation for my current Nursing Practice.

Today, I have 19+ years of nursing experience, primarily in High Risk OB, Maternal/Newborn Nursing, and in November of 2014, I began a new role as an RN/VN, OB specialist/Clincal & Theory/Simulation Instructor for Unitek College.

Recently, I returned to my hometown, after completing an Interim Management position in Turlock, CA. I am working per diem positions in out patient surgery, as well as at a local hospital in L&D, as I pursue a start~up idea, and research it's possible viability in the SF Bay Area.

I love learning, teaching, & sharing my nursing, life experiences, and general knowledge base, with RN/VN students, friends, family and colleagues.

My specialty and first love is High Risk OB, Teaching my patients and their families, how to care for their newborn, and most specifically how to create successful breastfeeding Mother's, while

considering age, socioeconomic factors, support, family size, demands on Mother, knowledge base, and assisting her in creating a, "Working Mom's," breastfeeding/pumping plan & nutritional menu, and meal planning, for optimal breast~milk production.

My hope is to make a difference in cultivating the next generation of highly skilled & well educated VN & RN's, through my love for OB & Evidence based nursing practice.

I continue to practice High~Risk OB, maintaining an up to date knowledge base, I can pass on to my students, patients, & simply because, being part of bringing new life into the world is an absolutely blessing at the end of the day!

I truly believe Nursingis the best career I could have chosen. #LOVE A NURSE!:)

Experience

Concentric Healthcare Staffing High Risk OB, Travel RN August 2019 - Present (1 year) Watsonville, California

Assess, Monitor, Manage High Risk OB plan of care, for Mother's and fetus' in the High Risk OB setting, Antepartum, Postpartum

Fast Staff Nursing~ US Nursing
Traveling RN/Per Diem RN
June 2012 - Present (8 years 2 months)
Various Hospitals throughout Northern & Southern CA

Infusion of Care
Infusion RN~IVIG Home Infusions
March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)
Westminster, California

Perform Mobile, in home, office, school IVIG Infusions throughout, Monterey Bay, SF Bay Area, Sacramento,& surrounding areas.

Lotus Learning , LLC
Owner|CEO|Director of Learning & Development

March 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months)

Campbell, California

Lotus Learning, LLC

Owner | CEO | Director of Learning & Development

Unitek College

OB Specialist, RN/VN Clinical & Theory Instructor, OB High Fidelity Simulator Instructor

November 2014 - Present (5 years 9 months)

San Jose, California

RN/VN-OB Clinial, Theory, & Simulation Instructor @ Unitek College

Tenet Healthcare

Nurse Manager

January 2019 - September 2019 (9 months)

Emanuel Medical Center, Turlock, CA

Manage 4 units within Women's and Children center; L&D, MB, NICU, Pediatrics.

Good Samaritan Hospital - San Jose, CA Clinical Coordinator/Manager of Labor & Delivery, Postpartum, Antepartum

August 2017 - October 2017 (3 months)

San Jose, California

Stanford Health Care

RN, BSN ~ Stanford Health Care ~ Infertility Clinic

September 2016 - February 2017 (6 months)

Sunnyvale, California

R.E.i. Clinic @ Stanford~ Reproduction Clinic

Life Center Birthcenter

Birthing Center RN, Birth Center Coordinator

April 2013 - January 2014 (10 months)

Sacramento, California Area

Coordinated staffing, maintained staff competencies, purchasing of supplies, marketing, training, assisted in birthing center delivery & recovery.

Kaiser Permanente

RNII, BSN

February 2004 - April 2011 (7 years 3 months)

Sacramento~Roseville, CA

High Risk OB, High Risk Antepartum, Charge Nurse MB/antepartum, Mother~Baby, PACU, OR circulator, level II NICU, NBN. Currently, RN OB clinical, EPIC Super User; provided staff training during hospital wide EMR conversion, Instructor @ Kaiser, San Leandro for Unitek College.

Education

University of Nevada-Reno

Bachelor of Science, Nursing, Nursing; focus on Maternal/Child Health and Neonatal Nurse/Nursing \cdot (1997 - 2000)

University of Nevada, Reno ~ Orvis School of Nursing
BSN~Bachelor's degree in Science & Nursing , Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse